fb.org 2018-06-30

# 

American Farm Bureau Federation (“AFBF”) values individual privacy and we want to give visitors to our fb.org website (the “Site”) the opportunity to know what information we collect about them and how they can limit the use of personally-identifiable information beyond the purposes for which they first provided it.

At all times, AFBF reserves the right to disclose information where required by law or to comply with valid legal process (such as a search warrant, subpoena or court order), to protect AFBF’s rights or property, including without limitation in the event of a transfer of control of AFBF or substantially all of its assets, or during emergencies when safety is at risk.

Whenever we change our policy, we will let you know by prominently posting a notice on our home page. Since these policy change notices last only for a limited time, however, you should check this Privacy Policy periodically to see if there have been any changes.

By accessing the Site, you acknowledge that you have read and understand this Privacy Policy, as well as our Terms and Conditions of Use, accept them, and agree to be legally bound by them. You should not use the site if you have any objections to this Privacy Policy, or any of the Terms & Conditions.

### Children’s Privacy

AFBF does not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. If AFBF obtains knowledge that it has personally identifiable information about a child under 13 in retrievable form, AFBF will immediately destroy that information, and delete that information from its files.

_Types of Information We Collect and How We Use It_

### Personally Identifiable Information

If you are over the age of 13, we may collect your name, address, phone number and email address if you communicate that information to us voluntarily. We will not share your personally identifiable information with anyone outside AFBF and its affiliated companies.

We may use this information to i) respond to an email or other inquiry or request from you, ii) to help improve our Site and our services, iii) to customize your experience at our Site, or iv) to send updates or notices about our organization. We may also combine this information with other generally or publicly available information to help us identify visitors’ preferences or interests.

### Non-Personal Information

In some cases, when you visit our Site, we may also collect information that is non-personally identifiable information or information that, by itself, cannot be used to identify or contact you. Examples of this type of information include the type of Internet browser or computer operating system you use, the date and time you visited our Site, the pages you accessed, the name of the Site from which you linked to our Site and other anonymous data involving your use of our site. We use this information to analyze trends and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. This information is not linked to any personally identifiable information.

### How We Use Cookies

We use “cookies” and other tracking technologies to enhance your online experience. These technologies help us recognize repeat visitors, facilitate the visitor’s ongoing access to and use of the Site, and track usage behavior and compile aggregate data that can lead to website improvements. If you do not want information collected through the use of cookies, you can deny or accept the cookie feature using a simple procedure available in most browsers. If you block cookies, however, you may lose some website functionality.

### Data Integrity and Security

We make reasonable commercial efforts to keep any information you provide as secure as possible. Only authorized employees or agents are permitted to have access to personally identifiable data about website visitors, and that access is limited to what is reasonably needed to perform an employee’s responsibilities, such as providing updates or notices or customer service.

### Third Party Collectors of Information

This Privacy Statement addresses only the use and disclosure of information we collect from you. Any information you disclose to a third party, such as other users or advertisers, is subject to that party’s Privacy Statement. We encourage you to ask questions before you disclose your personal information to others.

### Comments and Questions

If you have any questions or comments about the AFBF Privacy Policy, or if you have submitted personally identifiable information through this site and would like to access such information or to have that information corrected, please contact us at webmaster@fb.org, or call us at (202) 406-3600.
